/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data12_3', {
    title: '12.3 Round Decimals',
    path: '12.3-round-decimals',
    children: [{
        title: 'Round Decimals',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this decimal number to the indicated place value: Nearest Hundredths place}}}{\\row{\\str{0.96139}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{0.96}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{0.96139}{4}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Round Decimals',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this decimal number to the indicated place value: Nearest Tenths place}}}{\\row{\\str{5.52887}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{5.5}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{5.52887}{5}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Round Decimals',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this decimal number to the indicated place value: Nearest Hundredths place}}}{\\row{\\str{6.2412}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{6.24}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{6.2412}{3}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Round Decimals',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this decimal number to the indicated place value: Nearest Ten-Thousandths place}}}{\\row{\\str{1.96139}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{1.9614}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{1.96139}{2}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Round Decimals',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this decimal number to the indicated place value: Nearest Ones place}}}{\\row{\\str{1.68}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{2}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{1.68}{3}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Round Decimals',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this decimal number to the indicated place value: Nearest Tenths place}}}{\\row{\\str{7.19824}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{7.2}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{7.19824}{5}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Round Decimals',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this decimal number to the indicated place value: Nearest Tenths place}}}{\\row{\\str{10.9563}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{11.0}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{10.9563}{4}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Round Decimals',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this decimal number to the indicated place value: Nearest Tens place}}}{\\row{\\str{49.1}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{50}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{49.1}{3}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Round Decimals',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this decimal number to the indicated place value: Nearest Hundredths place}}}{\\row{\\str{16.4118}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{16.41}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{16.4118}{3}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Round Decimals',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Round this decimal number to the indicated place value: Nearest Thousandths place}}}{\\row{\\str{7.7195}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{7.720}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\placevalue{7.7195}{2}{showanswer}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, ]
});
